Faculty Reference; Collection ua950.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- S, 1851-2005; 19
  - Staley, Harry C., Undated (Box 38, Folder 58)
  - Stallman, Esther, Undated (Box 38, Folder 59)
  - Standing, Theodore G., Undated (Box 38, Folder 60)
  - Stanfill, Nancy, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 61)
  - Stamatel, Janet, Undated (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - Stankiewicz, Richard, Undated (Box 38, Folder 63)
  - Starr, David, Undated (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - Stauffer, Donald, Undated (Box 38, Folder 65)
  - Stauffer, Donald Barlow, Undated (Box 38, Folder 66)
  - Stanisky, Leonard, Undated (Box 38, Folder 67)
  - Stearns, Richard E., Undated (Box 38, Folder 68)
  - Steen, Ivan D., Undated (Box 38, Folder 69)
  - Steen, Ivan D., Undated (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - Stefl-Mabry, Joette, Undated (Box 38, Folder 71)
  - Steffens, Georgette, Undated (Box 38, Folder 72)
  - Steger, Barbara M., Undated (Box 38, Folder 73)
  - Steger, Joseph A., Undated (Box 38, Folder 74)
  - Eleanor, Stein, Undated (Box 38, Folder 75)
  - Stein, Theodore J., Undated (Box 38, Folder 76)
  - Steinberg, Ronnie, Undated (Box 38, Folder 77)
  - Steinberg, Ronnie, Undated (Box 38, Folder 78)
  - Steinbock, Bonnie, Undated (Box 38, Folder 79)
  - Stelzer, Leigh, Undated (Box 38, Folder 80)
  - Stenger, Carol P., Undated (Box 38, Folder 81)
  - Stern, Helman I., Undated (Box 38, Folder 82)
  - Stern, Kenneth, Undated (Box 38, Folder 83)
  - Stern, Marilyn, Undated (Box 38, Folder 84)
  - Stern, Susan, Undated (Box 38, Folder 85)
  - Stessin, Michael I., Undated (Box 38, Folder 86)
  - Stevens, Dennis, Undated (Box 38, Folder 87)
  - Stevens, Gregory I., Undated (Box 38, Folder 88)
  - Stevens, Jane E., Undated (Box 38, Folder 89)
  - Stevens, Kathryn (Jerum), Undated (Box 38, Folder 90)
  - Stevens, Laurel Sloat, Undated (Box 38, Folder 91)
  - Stevenson, Gordon, Undated (Box 38, Folder 92)
  - Stevenson, Sara H., Undated (Box 38, Folder 93)
  - Stever, Gertrude, Undated (Box 38, Folder 94)
  - Stewart, Bruce, Undated (Box 38, Folder 95)
  - Stewart, Bruce, Undated (Box 38, Folder 96)
  - Stewart, Caro- Beth, Undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Stewart, Jason, Undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Stewart, Jason, Undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Stewart, Jimmie, Jason, Undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Stewart, Margaret M., Undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Stewart, Margaret McBride, Undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Stewart, Mary Ellen, Undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Stewart, Ronald, Undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Stewart, Ronald, Undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Stewart, Thomas R., Undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Stewart, Thomas R., Undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Stewart, William C., Undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Stewart, William, Jr., Undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Stienstra, Arthur L., Undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Stierer, Robert A., Undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Stierer, Robert A., Undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Stigliani, William M., Undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Stock, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Stockin, Bruce C., Undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Stoessinger, John G., Undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Stokes, Dean Ellen C., Undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Stone, David E., Undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Stone, Dianna, Undated (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Stone, Edward Durell, Undated (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Stone, Lois, Undated (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Stone, Romero Eugene, Undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Articles "Stoneman, Kate" bibliography, Undated (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Stong, C.L., Undated (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Story, Harold S., Undated (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Story, Harold S., 1927-2001 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Stout, Ronald M., Undated (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Stout, Ronald M., Undated (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Stout, Ronald M., Undated (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Strach, Patricia, Undated (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Strachan, Cherie (Jayne), Undated (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Strait, David, Undated (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Stratton, Howard H., Undated (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Stratton, Howard H., Undated (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Strelka, Joseph, Undated (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Streun, Eleanor D., Undated (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Strogartz, David, Undated (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Stross, Raymond, Undated (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Stross, Raymond G., Undated (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Strzalkowski, Tomek, Undated (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Stump, Paul, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Stump, Roger W., Undated (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Stutz, John, Undated (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Suarez, Irma, Undated (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Suchon, Kathleen, Undated (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Sugarman, Robert, Undated (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Sullivan, Anne, Undated (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Sullivan, Dennis, Undated (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Sullivan, Dennis, Undated (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Sullivan, Richard W., Undated (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Suls, Jerry M., Undated (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - Sun, Chih-Ree, Undated (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - Sun, Helen, Undated (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - Supple, Susan, Undated (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - Sutherland, Marcia, Undated (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - Sutton, George H., Undated (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Suzuki, Kunihiro, Undated (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Svare, Bruce B., Undated (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - Savre, Bruce B., Undated (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - Swan, Karen, Undated (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - Swan, L. Alex, Undated (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - Swann, John, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  - Swanoon, Philip, Undated (Box 39, Folder 67)
  - Swanstrom, Todd, Undated (Box 39, Folder 68)
  - Swanstrom, Todd F., Undated (Box 39, Folder 69)
  - Sweeney, Deirdre, Undated (Box 39, Folder 70)
  - Sweet, Jeffrey, Undated (Box 39, Folder 71)
  - Sweet, Richard, Undated (Box 39, Folder 72)
  - Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 39, Folder 73)
  - Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 39, Folder 74)
  - Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 39, Folder 75)
  - Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 39, Folder 76)
  - Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 39, Folder 77)
  - Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Sweetser, Albert G., Undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Swider, Andrew L., Undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Swiny, Stuart, Undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick Inauguration Ceremony, 1991 April 5 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, Undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, Undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, Undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, 1990-1995 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick Photos, Undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick Photos, Undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick - Temple University background, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick Inauguration, 1991 April 5 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick Biographical Sketch, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Swygert, H.P. Biographical Sketch, 1993 March (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick NYS Special Commission on Educational Structure, Policies and Practices v.II, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick New York State Special Commission on Educational Structures, Policies and Practices v.I Report, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick Vita, 1993 August (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick New York State Special Commission on Educational Structures, Policies and Practices v.III Report, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick Biographical Sketch, 1993 June-1993 August (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick New York State Special Commission on Educational Structure, Policies and Practices V.III Report, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick Moreland Act Commission, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick - Post U. at A. (see also Howard University Folder), 1995 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick - Howard University, 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick NYS State Special Commission on Educational Structure, Policies and Practices V.IV, Undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Swygert, H. Patrick Inauguration, Undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Symons, James M., Undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Syphax, Richard, Undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Szalczer, Eszter, Undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Szaro, Ben G., Undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Szelest, Bruce, Undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Szoverffy, Joseph, Undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Szulgit, John, Undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
- T, 1851-2005; 20
  - Taber, Thomas D., Undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Tabner, Mary F., Undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Tanguay, Janet, Undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Tanzman, Melinda S., Undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Tamor, Lynne, Undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Tan, T.K., 1971 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Tang, T.K., Undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Tantillo, Richard C., Undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Tarasevitch, Moses, Undated (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Tarlton, Charles, Undated (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Tarlton, Charles D., Undated (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Tarsa, Mary, Undated (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Tashman, Mildred, Undated (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Tastor, Richard, Undated (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Tavantzis, Thomas N., Undated (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Tavarozzi, Michael, Undated (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Tavarozzi, Michael A., Undated (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Tayi, Girl Kumar, Undated (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Taylor, Abigail, Undated (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Taylor, Lisa, Undated (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Taylor, Myron, Undated (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Taylor, Myron, Undated (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Taylor, Ronald G., Undated (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Taylor, Stephen, Undated (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Taylor, Wallace, Undated (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Tedeschi, Henry, Undated (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Tedeschi, Henry, Undated (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Tedeschi, James, Undated (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Tedeschi, James T., Undated (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Teevan, Richard C., Undated (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Teevan, Richard, Undated (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Temesvary, Stephan Christoph, Undated (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Temkin, Sefton D., Undated (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Temkin, Sefton, Undated (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Tenenbaum, Scott, Undated (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Tennon, Howard A., Undated (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Teplitz, Charles J., Undated (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Terenzini, Patrick T., Undated (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Tesch, Frederick, Undated (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Testi, Giorgio, Undated (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Testo, Joseph, Undated (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Testo, Joseph, Undated (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Theophilides, Christos, Undated (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Therrien, John, Undated (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Therrien, John, Undated (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Thiel, Brad, Undated (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Thiel, Bradley L., Undated (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Thiemke, Sue, Undated (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Thomas, Chester B., Undated (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Thomas, Chester B., Undated (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Thomas, David A., Undated (Box 41, Folder 67)
  - Thomas, Edward, Undated (Box 41, Folder 68)
  - Thomas, Edward S. Jr., Undated (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - Thomas, James A., Undated (Box 41, Folder 70)
  - Thomas, James A., Undated (Box 41, Folder 71)
  - Thompson, Dell, Undated (Box 41, Folder 72)
  - Thompson, Frank, Undated (Box 41, Folder 73)
  - Thompson, Lisa, Undated (Box 41, Folder 74)
  - Thompson, Harold W., Undated (Box 41, Folder 75)
  - Thompson, Jean Univ. Lib - Monographic Cataloger, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 76)
  - Thompson, Julius E., Undated (Box 41, Folder 77)
  - Thompson, Michael D., Undated (Box 41, Folder 78)
  - Thompson, Michael P., Undated (Box 41, Folder 79)
  - Thompson, Steven, Undated (Box 41, Folder 80)
  - Thornberry, Terrence, Undated (Box 41, Folder 81)
  - Thornberry, Terrence, Undated (Box 41, Folder 82)
  - Thorncraft, Christopher, Undated (Box 41, Folder 83)
  - Thorne, Clifton, Undated (Box 41, Folder 84)
  - Thornton, Jerome, Undated (Box 41, Folder 85)
  - Thornton, Kathleen, Undated (Box 41, Folder 86)
  - Thorstensen, Robert Edwin, Undated (Box 41, Folder 87)
  - Thorton, Maurice, Undated (Box 41, Folder 88)
  - Thyagarajan, S., Undated (Box 41, Folder 89)
  - Tibbetts, John Ralph, Undated (Box 41, Folder 90)
  - Tickner, Fred, Undated (Box 41, Folder 91)
  - Tieman, David, Undated (Box 41, Folder 92)
  - Tieman, Suzannah, Undated (Box 41, Folder 93)
  - Tieszen, Derk V., Undated (Box 41, Folder 94)
  - Tillman, Dennis, Undated (Box 41, Folder 95)
  - Tine, John, Undated (Box 41, Folder 96)
  - Tisdale, Walter M., Undated (Box 41, Folder 97)
  - Titterington, Donald M., Undated (Box 41, Folder 98)
  - Tittnich, Michael, Undated (Box 41, Folder 99)
  - Tobin, Sheldon S., Undated (Box 41, Folder 100)
  - Toch, Hans, Undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Toch, Hans, Undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Toigo, Romolo, Undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Tolbert, Ira, Undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Tolnay, Stewart, Undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Tompkins, Phillip, Undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Tompkins, Phillip K., Undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Tooker, Elisabeth J., Undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Topal, Alan, Undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Topal, Janet, Undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Torda, Alice, Undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Torrente Ballester, Gonzalo, Undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Tortorici, Ralph, Undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Toscano, John A., Undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Toscano, John, Undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Toscano, Paul J., Undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Toseland, Ronald W., Undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Toseland, Ronald W., Undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Totaro, Robert, Undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Trachtenberg, Barry, Undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Traunstein, Donald, Undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Traver, Stephen W., Undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Travis, Jeffrey L., Undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Traylor, Suzanne, Undated (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Treadway, Ann, Undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Trementozzi, Miriam, Undated (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Tricart, Jean, Undated (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Triggiani, Roberto, Undated (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Trinci, Rita D., Undated (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Trubitt, Lisa V., Undated (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - True, Joel, Undated (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - True, Joel M., Undated (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Truscott, Frederick H., Undated (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Truscott, Frederick, Undated (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Tryon, Richard D., Undated (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Tucker, Clara Jean, Undated (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Tucker, John Edward, Undated (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Tuecke, John E., Undated (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Tullock, Anthony, Undated (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Tully, George, Undated (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Tuohey, Hugh J., Undated (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Turek, Kathy, Undated (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Turi, Rich, Undated (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Turnage, David, Undated (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Turner, Ann, Undated (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Turner, Edward, Undated (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Turner, Edward C., Undated (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Turner, Nura, Undated (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Turner, Suzanne, Undated (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Turruisi, Robert J., Undated (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Twombley, Josey, Undated (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Twomey, Daniel, Undated (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Tyckoson, David A., Undated (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Tyckoson, David A., 1989 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Tyckoson, David Arthur, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 55)
- U, 1851-2005; 21
  - Ukeritis, Miriam D., Undated (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Ullrich, Helen Elizabeth, 1970-1974 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Unger, Donald, Undated (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Unger, James, Undated (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Upal, J.S., 1986 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Uppal, Jogindar S., Undated (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Urbach, Leslie, Undated (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - Urofsky, Melvin, Undated (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Urquhart, Nina M., Undated (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - Usher, Peter D., Undated (Box 42, Folder 65)
- V, 1851-2005; 22
  - Vaillancourt, Pauline M., Undated (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - Vaillancourt, Pauline M., Undated (Box 42, Folder 67)
  - Valentine, Gertrude Crissey, Undated (Box 42, Folder 68)
  - Valentis, Mary, Undated (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - Vallila, Marja, Undated (Box 42, Folder 70)
  - Valverde, Gilbert, Undated (Box 42, Folder 71)
  - Van Den Haag, Ernest, Undated (Box 42, Folder 72)
  - Van Den Haag, Ernest, Undated (Box 42, Folder 73)
  - Vander Kolk, Charles, Undated (Box 42, Folder 74)
  - Vandervort, Lucinda A., Undated (Box 42, Folder 75)
  - Van Horne, Gertrude, Undated (Box 42, Folder 76)
  - Van Kleeck, E.R., Undated (Box 42, Folder 77)
  - Van Landingham, Michael, Undated (Box 42, Folder 78)
  - Van Liew, Marion S., 1913 January-1920 June (Box 42, Folder 79)
  - Van Nostrand, Gene, Undated (Box 42, Folder 80)
  - Van Ordeu, Janis H., Undated (Box 42, Folder 81)
  - Van Patten, Grant, Undated (Box 42, Folder 82)
  - Van Patten, Grant, Undated (Box 42, Folder 83)
  - Van Schoor, Thomas J., Undated (Box 42, Folder 84)
  - Van Soest, Gardy, Undated (Box 42, Folder 85)
  - Van Ullen, Mary, Undated (Box 42, Folder 86)
  - Van Ullen, Mary, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 87)
  - VanValhenburg, Carol, Undated (Box 42, Folder 88)
  - Van Voorst, James R., Undated (Box 42, Folder 89)
  - Varadarajam, Poondi, Undated (Box 42, Folder 90)
  - Varanasi, P., Undated (Box 42, Folder 91)
  - Vatalaro, Charles, Undated (Box 42, Folder 92)
  - Vayo, Michael, Undated (Box 42, Folder 93)
  - Vecchione, Al, Undated (Box 42, Folder 94)
  - Vegter, Amy, Undated (Box 42, Folder 95)
  - Vellis, Peter, Undated (Box 42, Folder 96)
  - Vellis, Peter, Undated (Box 42, Folder 97)
  - Vellutino, Frank, Undated (Box 42, Folder 98)
  - Vellutino, Frank R., Undated (Box 42, Folder 99)
  - Vellutino, Frank R., Undated (Box 42, Folder 100)
  - Verentzioti, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 42, Folder 101)
  - Vegari, Sandra M., Undated (Box 42, Folder 102)
  - Verhoff, Kimberly, Undated (Box 42, Folder 103)
  - Vermeulen, Sabina T., Undated (Box 42, Folder 104)
  - Verschoor, Irving A., 1913-1987 (Box 42, Folder 105)
  - Via, Barbara, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Via, Barbara J., Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Vial, Fernand, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Viana, Charles, Undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Vickery, William D., Undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Videka-Sherman, Lynn M., Undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Villela, Sally Crimmins, Undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Vinci, Liza, Undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Vinciguerra, Anthony, Undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Vitale, James E., Undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Viteritti, Joseph, Undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Vives, Roberto, Undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - State University of New York at Albany, A Short History, Undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Voelker, Charles, Undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Vogt, Paul W., Undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Volk, Gregory, Undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - von der Heide, Dina B., Undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Vonnegut, Bernard, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Vonnegut, Bernard, Undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Vonnegut, Bernard, Undated (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Vonnegut, Bernard, Undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Vontoslos, Nicholas, Undated (Box 43, Folder 22)
- W, 1851-2005; 23
  - Wacholder, Stephanie, Undated (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Waddington, Dan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Wagner, Alan P., Undated (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Wagner, Christine Konen, Undated (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Wagner, David d, Undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Wagner, Gerard, 1970 June 5 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Wagner, Janet M., Undated (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Wakin, B. Bertha, Undated (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Wakin, B. Bertha, Undated (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Walcek, Christopher, Undated (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Walker, Adam A., Undated (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Walker, Andrew, Undated (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Walker, Bailus, Undated (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Walker, Bailus, Undated (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Walker, Brita, Undated (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Walker, Franklin, Undated (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Walker, Franklin V., Undated (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Walker, Galal, Undated (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Walker, Melanie J., Undated (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Walker, Theresa, Undated (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Walker, Thomas, Undated (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Walker, Vic, Undated (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Wall, Joseph F., Undated (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Wallace, Dwight T., Undated (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Wallace, Edith O., Undated (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Wallace, Paul, Undated (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Wallace, Paul, Undated (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Walmsley, Sean A., Undated (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Walser, James N., Undated (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - Walsh, Karen, Undated (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - Walsh, Thomas J., Undated (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - Walther, Eric G., Undated (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - Walton, A. Ronald, Undated (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - Walton, Sam, Undated (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - Waltz, Mary Anne L., 1994 (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - Walz, Frederick G., Undated (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - Wang, Ing-Nang, Undated (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - Wang, Sho-Ya, Undated (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - Wang, Wei-Chyung, Undated (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - Wapner, John H., Undated (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - Ward, John Paul, Undated (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - Ward, J. Paul, Undated (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - Ward, Russel A., Undated (Box 43, Folder 65)
  - Warner, Demita (Dee), Undated (Box 43, Folder 66)
  - Warner, Lynn, Undated (Box 43, Folder 67)
  - Warner, Maria H., Undated (Box 43, Folder 68)
  - Warren, Bruce D., Undated (Box 43, Folder 69)
  - Warren, Marguerite, Undated (Box 43, Folder 70)
  - Warren, Marguerite Q., Undated (Box 43, Folder 71)
  - Wasby, Stephen, Undated (Box 43, Folder 72)
  - Wasby, Stephen L., Undated (Box 43, Folder 73)
  - Washington, Lamar, Undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Wasielewski, Terrance L., Undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Waterbury, Eleanor, Undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Waterman, Caroline, Undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Watkins, Stephen G., Undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Wayne, Raymie, Undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Webb, John W., Undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Webb, John W., 1979 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Weber, Brom, Undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Weber, Rose- Marie, Undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Webster, Robert O., Undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Weeks, Richard, Undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Weinberg, Anne A., Undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Weinberg, Jerry, Undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Weinberg, Martin S., Undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Weinberg, Saul, Undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Weiner, Albert, Undated (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Weinstein, Frederick Daniel, Undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Weinstock, Susan Jan, Undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Weishar, Judy, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Weisman, Robert, Undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Weisman, Robert, Undated (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Weiss, Rabbi Avi, Undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Weitz, Anna, Undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Welch, Edward, Undated (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Welch, John T., Undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Welch, Kenneth, Undated (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Welch, Lewis P., Undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Welch, Lewis P., 1971 October 4 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Welch, Lewis P., Undated (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Welch, Linda, Undated (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Welch, Michael W., Undated (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Wells, Ralph, Undated (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Welsh, James, Undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Welsh, John T., Undated (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Welty, John D., Undated (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Werner, Alfred Charles, Undated (Box 44, Folder 37)